# Luca D'Ettorre

PHONE: 0857053152 • EMAIL: LDETTORRE@OUTLOOK.COM

#### **Profile**

Dynamic and motivated professional with 3+ years management experience in a fast paced high pressure environment. Now transitioning into Software Development having just completed a Full Stack Software Development Course at the Code Institute, Dublin. Eager to apply my extensive background in people management, critical thinking and progressive attitude to a new workplace.

## **Qualification**

Completion of Full Stack Software Development Course from the Code Institute, Dublin. Course syllabus: <a href="https://www.codeinstitute.net/classroom/">https://www.codeinstitute.net/classroom/</a>

#### **Skills**

Proficient in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Python as well as working with Frameworks such as Flask, Django and Bootstrap. I have also done some work implementing databases with MLab and payment features with Stripe.

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/ldettorre">https://github.com/ldettorre</a>

#### Work Experience

#### <u>Operations Manager</u> <u>Roma Takeaway, Loughlinstown.</u>

<u>June 2014 - April 2018</u>

- Manage a diverse multilingual team in a fast paced and time sensitive environment.
- Resolve disputes and disagreements amongst staff and with the public.
- Ensure compliance with relevant authorities and have correct paperwork completed.
- Research and Develop business relationships with suppliers.
- Providing a leadership support function to the teams and motivating staff to achieve efficiency goals.
- Develop and coach a reliable team to a level of competence, clarifying and delegating direct responsibility of their role throughout each day or week.
- All Cash handling, card transactions, banking and transaction/sales reporting.

#### **Supervisor**

#### February 2012 - July 2014

### Roma Takeaway, Loughlinstown.

- Scheduling (planning, assigning and directing work) to meet business demands to ensure optimal operations and customer satisfaction during all business hours.
- Document and follow up on all processes in order to implement improvements.
- Responsible for the opening and closure of the store following procedures.

# Luca D'Ettorre

PHONE: 0857053152 • EMAIL: LDETTORRE@OUTLOOK.COM

<u>Kitchen Assistant</u> <u>Papa Lino's, Bray, Co.Wicklow</u> February 2011 - February 2012

Education

Blackrock College 2004-2010

LinkedIn Profile

https://www.linkedin.com/in/lucadettorre/

References available on request